Thank you for watching!
Here you go. Here we go.
Hallo! Ste this time is with Shigeru Akiyama of Tsubaki Factory, Beyooooonds, and Yuiyo Sato of Seasonings.
Please stay with us until the end of this issue, as we will be presenting you with two such people.
Tsubaki Factory is pleased to announce the release of its third album, 3rd MOMENT, on February 21.
It has been three years since the last album was released, and we have always dreamed of releasing an album among the members,
I am very happy that this is possible,
There are 4 new songs in the album,
They are all very different genres,
Some songs are exciting at a live concert, and others are sad songs that are typical of Tsubaki,
There are also some cool rap-like songs that have never been done before,
It's really a lot of fun,
I hope many people will listen to it.
And Hello! Project has started Hello! Project 2024 Winter 3 of Us.
We are on the same team A,
Morning Musume。 24, Tsubaki Factory and Beyooooonds.
There are cover songs that are unique to Halocon,
We had a dance club this time as well, and we rehearsed together,
I like the dancing a lot for the chance to sing,
It's a genre of dance, or rather, I really like watching it,
I was rehearsing and absorbing things as we rehearsed.
It's a lot of fun.
It's fun.
Your dances are really inspiring me,
I will do my best to make it hot and exciting.
Now please watch this video.
Hi.
Dancing Singing Exciting
galaxy
Galaxy Galaxy
Shubidubidubidubigalaxy
I knew it. Gottari, egoism, gottari.
I knew it. I'm going to pull in. I don't feel safe here.
Put your clothes on your hands, Vaccine.
This hair, Idly. He's bluffing.
Gattari, idly, bottom face, endorsement.
He wanted me to stay as I was.
You are a hero for saying it.
therefore
Let's hug it out.
More beautiful at the camp.
writing off (a debt)
Life is theater.
What a wonderful moment!
be able to guess the right answer
Ladies and Gentlemen
A gradation that attracts the attention of the entire universe
Hot Dramatic Love Comedy with Gigantic HP
The star of the show, of course.
It's you!
Yes, let's love the Mystery Demon.
4K staff jumps in. Oysters kiss the rim.
Life is passionate.
4K Staff Shoes
After is the Giga Medal
Let's light the lamp for a lifetime.
I'm already writing the whole alias.
Let's write down the numbers!
Timing is the root of iron
Oh, my God, Ayer.
Every moment matters.
Galaxy Galaxy
Shubi Shubi Shubi Shubi Galaxy
Switch is my world
Slicky, approaching Topelzai.
Thanks for all your hard work.
Maama Akiyama of Tsubaki Factory and Yutana Satoyo of Bion's Seasonings present "Halo ! Sta!
I'd like to tell you a little bit about each other from here.
I will ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer them in a quick tempo!
So, are we ready?
I'll go then.
Utano's makeup-based installations have been well received.
What is the point of today's makeup?
How to apply the tip
Utano, who obtained the Personal Colorist Certificate Level 1.
Tell me the perfect color for me, Maama Akiyama.
green
What?
Seasonings formed three years ago now.
How would you describe the current Seasonings in a few words?
trust
I'm soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
What do you struggle with in dance?
Stiff knees
What?
Bions celebrates 5th anniversary of major debut this year
What would you like to accomplish with your group this year?
outdoor concert
Ooh.
Oh no, it's all over.
I'd like to ask them one by one.
The Personal Colorist Certificate Level 1 is
What is it?
Yes, sir.
The Personal Colorist Certificate is a test for personal colorists.
Learn about color science and the history of color and stuff like that.
The combination of this color and this color
I hear it looks great.
Or look a little cool.
Learning those color combinations and
It's a personal color that suits each and every person.
I'm sometimes called Brubeck at home.
He said he is a person who can discern such things.
Oh, my gosh.
In it, I am green.
Yes, sir.
A little unexpected
that is so
And of course, red looks great on you.
Something else unexpected.
I thought it would be a very glamorous color.
I chose green.
Well, I don't know about personal color now.
I think it's pretty prevalent.
I've been thinking about it a lot.
It's like, why don't you just wear whatever color you want?
That's what I thought.
I wanted to know what colors would suit me best.
I'm very happy to hear that it's green, and I'm very happy to hear that it's green.
Just a little after this recording is done.
I thought I'd like to hear more details.
Okay, one more thing.
Yes, sir.
What I struggle with in dance
Knee?
Knees.
Stiff knees.
Oh, wow.
I've been told that I'm pretty hip when I'm not careful.
That's right.
No thanks, so I'm always conscious of it, and I'm always aware of it, and I'm always aware of my hips.
I try to keep my knees bent tight.
Stiff knees, I mean.
I know you are.
I guess it's just a habit.
I have to be aware of it to bend it.
I don't make you feel this way.
I've always been a cool performer.
No, it's really cool.
I'll do my best.
Now, questions for Mr. Akiyama after the VTR.
Hallo! Ste.
GETCHU!
Shall we dance?
Bach-chang, bach-chang, bach-chang, bach-chang, drink tea.
Home!
Ocha no Oma! First album Channel 1 now on sale!
Hallo! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask Mr. Akiyama a question.
Yes.
Are you ready?
It's okay.
Mr. Akiyama shortened his hair at the end of the year.
Are there any fashion styles you would like to try with a short cut?
Yes. It is a fashion that shows the décolleté.
What is the theme of Mao Akiyama for this year 2024?
variety
The new album will be released next month on the 21st,
What do you personally think is the best part of 3rd Moment?
Yes, I have a song called "Power Flower". The song is called Power Flower, Now is the time to come together as one.
What genre of dance would you like to dance that you have never danced before?
Clamps.
Two months have passed since the new organization was formed. What do you think of your role in Tsubaki Factory now?
Live honestly. It is.
Yes, I would like to know if you have any questions. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I'm curious about all of them.
What fashion style would you like to try?
Yes.
Décolleté.
Yes, I did. Even when I had long hair, I might have worn fashion that showed off my décolleté,
It looks better when it is short.
It seems to look brighter.
I think it looks brighter,
I don't think I'll get a chance to wear it much,
I thought it would be fun to wear a dress or something for the shoot.
I'm looking forward to when the weather warms up.
Yes.
3 Moments, what to listen for.
Power Flower: It's a new song called "Now is the time to come together as one",
This song was written by Shock Eye,
This song sounds like the first rap song I mentioned earlier.
Wrap.
I was really surprised when I first heard it,
When Tsubaki Factory was formed, we had no idea that we would be asked to sing such a song,
I really feel empowered just by listening to it,
I also changed my singing style when I was singing,
I had been studying how to rap by watching various videos,
I hope everyone is looking forward to seeing how cool they look.
Hallo! Ste. I wonder if it will continue.
Hallo! Ste. 2013, September 20, 2013!
I am Masashi Natsuyaki.
I am Ruri Tamura of Juice-Juice.
Today is the day of completion, and I will do my best to finish it.
Yes, good luck.
What will you make this time?
I would like to make rainbow roll sushi.
I'm looking forward to it.
Have you ever made sushi rolls?
I've seen my mom make them before,
I'm really looking forward to it because I don't think I've done much of it myself.
Good.
I'm nervous.
Why? So people can see us?
Indeed. I've never made such a prohibited ball while being watched.
That's true.
I think it is good.
Where would you like to start this time?
Now it is time to wind it up.
Fun.
First of all, it's a bit strange because I do wrap,
Then, ask them to bring out a sheet of nori,
I want to do the whole thing thin.
It was so gooey.
Indeed.
You're sucking me dry.
When I do thin rolls, I intentionally leave this behind,
Today it's all because of the reverse roll.
Yes. Tightly packed.
Then here are the sesame seeds all over.
And then it was cut in half like this.
I think this is easier to do.
That's great. I'm going to do the opposite.
I'm not sure.
Quite the opposite already.
Yo.
Yes. Two cucumbers.
Two cucumbers.
Yes.
Add cream cheese, which goes well with Iburi School.
Absolutely delicious.
Yes.
Absolutely delicious. This is it.
Crab or cover it with avocado,
Is it like banned egg garbage?
Yes.
So, here we go.
Winding up.
It looks difficult to wind.
So I stop once, let the wrap float, and it becomes a convenience store onigiri.
Once up a bit, too.
Shall we bring it all to the front?
Yes, I do.
Yes.
Let's close this one a little tighter.
A little bit like candy here.
Yes.
Wow! Wow!
If you squeeze it too tightly, it will come out from the side,
Gently. Yes. That's good.
Yes.
Then let's take it out a bit.
Yes. I think it is good.
Yes.
It's beautiful.
Then open the wrap,
The more the groove here was coming up,
I'm going to cover it here,
Because you will not be able to see it,
Then here's the story,
If you put it vertically, only that guy will fit when you cut it.
It's like a diagonal overlap.
We're going one piece at a time, with an avocado in the middle.
Maybe avocado next to the salmon if possible.
It's better to layer them like this.
I'm sure you can see this sashimi too.
So the right side comes down.
Let's pull in a little closer.
That's quite a lot of minutes.
Luxury version
That's fine.
many
Good.
Put your chopsticks around here for a minute.
Also, wrap well.
A little to the side again, down again, up again.
And here we go again.
I'd say be careful here, especially with avocados and such.
If you squeeze it too hard, it will be crushed.
It's like grabbing one or the other and shaping it.
It will probably be fine.
(during the Edo period) plain kariginu
floorboards
Here's a near-biz point
point
Cute if we all do it together.
Yes, here it is. Let it rest in the fridge for 10 minutes.
Yes, sir.
This is chocolate.
If we keep going like this, it's going to get a little... soft.
Rice gets hard when it gets cold.
It's easier to make a clean cut after doing that.
I see
We'll let it rest in the fridge.
Put it over here.
Yes please.
(expression of) effort or strain
Have a nice day!
Have a good day
Okay, well, I can see the final product, so let's just keep working until we get it on the plate.
Now comes the hardest part of the day, cutting this whole wrap.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. If you take this off...
I'm working on it. It's going to spread out.
Yes, I'm a little caught up in the rap at the beginning.
Just drop it slowly and you'll be fine.
wrap
All the plastic wrap has been cut off.
Are you okay?
Wow, that's a tough one.
It's like the wrap is taking all the ingredients with it.
Let's take off the plastic wrap and give it a try.
One more thing and I'll be done.
I see, but it slides.
that's so, isn't it
The stories, you know, they just run away.
Difficult, difficult, difficult.
This may indeed be the most difficult one.
Oh, that's a tough one.
I'll just have to take one more goof.
It's all right.
live
by sheer strength
OK
good
number of nights
significant digit
good
if so
Put it back.
It's done.
Yes, and then wrap it up again.
And what shall we do?
These children.
These kids, too.
The extra is first place in the main, this one.
The extras.
in this way, then
This is a little something.
I want to make the most of it.
You'll need it, because I made it.
Here, at an angle.
Like rainbow rainbow.
Oh, good, good.
4 here first.
Yes, sir.
and put 3 on that side.
Let go of me for a second.
Yes, sir.
clean
That's fine.
Oh, yes, yes, I forgot.
With salmon roe on top.
Salmon roe, you could say it's a cancer.
Great.
I think it's good.
wow
Rainbow rolls and various extras are ready!
Completed!
Rainbow rolls are now complete.
Completed.
Well, what do you think, Ruru-chan?
It turned out very nicely, and the cross section is beautiful,
I'm glad it turned out so gorgeous.
I think it is quite gorgeous.
Then try it as soon as possible.
We will take it.
Will they eat it?
All of it?
Eat slowly and leisurely.
It is insanely delicious.
I put a lot of ingredients in it,
It's not like all of them are fighting so much,
It was a great match of everything,
It is so delicious.
Just looking at it, you can feel the deliciousness.
It was very refreshing to see that even though it was a sushi roll, it wasn't nori first,
It is delicious.
I challenged him by winding it in reverse.
I wonder how you would make it at a glance,
It's like when you do it, it's surprisingly like that.
Just turn it over.
It's not that hard.
That's probably enough about how to make it this time,
I don't think it was that difficult from Ruru's point of view, though,
How did you like it? Try it.
But it was a genre I hadn't done much in,
These gorgeous sushi, too,
I think it would be great for events and such,
I think I would be very happy to get something like this when my friends come over too,
I wanted to do it again.
It was great fun.
I'm glad. Really.
Please come again, Ruru-chan.
We look forward to seeing you. We look forward to seeing you.
Thank you very much.
These are Hello Kitchen.
Do you cook, Sato?
I cook quite a bit, but lately I've been getting into it,
Pork shabu soymilk miso pasta.
Looks delicious.
Potherb mustard, miso and pork go well together,
Something fashionable.
It is outstanding, and I am addicted to it and eat it at least three times a week.
Is it delicious? I want to eat it too.
Where is Mr. Ikeyama?
I am, I guess, particular about what I do.
I have a salad I've been making lately,
Really, though, it's not too unusual.
It might be very normal,
With lettuce, avocado, mozzarella cheese and prosciutto ham,
Then there is the garlic zero of eating raayu.
I love this so much,
I put this in and eat it with ponzu mayo,
I really think I don't need anything else after just one meal of this,
I eat this salad every day and it's so good,
Even if you don't like salads, give it a try,
I wish you could eat it.
Hallo! Ste.
Akyembomote of Tsubaki Factory
Beyooooonds, Yotana Satoyoshi of Seasonings presents Halo! Ste. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
We love to dance.
From my point of view, Utano's dancing is
It can be adapted to so many genres.
We both like the genre of wack.
Utano Chan is not bound by that genre.
I have the impression that it can be dyed to various kinds of music.
Also, you're soft.
you could say that
It's very soft and I'm a little hard.
I envy you very much for that.
Glad to hear it.
It's so cool.
From my point of view, Mr. Akiyama is
I think the very heavy movement is really nice.
Even though the movement is heavy, it is very natural.
It's more like, let's do it, let's do it.
It's very natural and easy to understand the points of various songs.
happy
I think the choreography of this song is very important.
The choreography here is meant to be impressive.
I'm not sure I'm getting it.
I think it's wonderful that you can tell so much.
Thank you.
This time, we will be using a selection of songs from each other's groups.
I chose a live video with some cool dance moves.
I would like to introduce them in order.
Yes, I, Akiyama, have chosen a cool dancing Beyooooonds song.
It's "hot."
Project 20th Anniversary
Project 2019 Winter New Age video for your viewing pleasure!
Go ahead.
They are all so young! So young!
I want to be there!
Free here?
Yes, we are. I'm already free.
This freebie was amazing. I was so surprised. When I saw it.
No 80% and no choreography.
I don't have 80%.
There is no hate with me.
Project had never had a song like that before, so I was really shocked when I saw it.
I was impressed by the reaction of the seniors when we did this rehearsal for the first time.
I'll never forget it. Really.
And it's so intense!
That's right.
I thought it would be tiring.
This is a bad idea.
One song.
See, it's already great! Now.
I wish they would show more. Here they come!
Amazing!!! Jumping after moving and turning like that is amazing!
Yes, you have seen it, but I really miss it.
When I saw the rehearsals after Uta-no-chan and Miu-chan joined the group, I knew that Hello! Project's music has so many freestyles,
I thought to myself, "Is this really the first time it's been hot?
I thought that the teacher who choreographed the piece said the choreography because the two of them were able to dance,
It is a view of the world that only the two of you can create, and also in the middle it seems as if the two of you are fighting against each other,
Dance battle.
It was also really cool, and I would like to cover it someday since I like dancing so much.
Utano, you put in a lot of back dancing, so I did the same.
I thought that someday I would like to work with Utano and myself.
Next, I chose a song by Tsubaki Factory, whose dance moves are cool, and there is no mistake, I don't cry.
Tsubaki Factory Concert Tour 2023 Autumn Atarayo
Riko Yamagishi & Yume Kishimoto's Graduation Special You will see a video of Dawn.
Go ahead!
I really like the sound here.
It is so cool.
I like the intro a lot,
Yes, I'm glad.
With Mr. Tsubaki with his cool tunes,
I felt that Tsubaki-san, with his pure and elegant music, was a hybrid,
Really?
It's cool.
Listening to this music is also very much like a dance lesson and the first time,
Align everyone in various details,
I think it was a very difficult dance.
I thought it was cool that it was so dynamic and yet aligned.
Glad to hear it.
I see it all the time.
The expressions on their faces are amazingly wonderful,
I would want a camera for all of them.
I'd certainly like to do something like that once.
Stay tuned for the next installment!
The soundtrack is quite detailed.
Yes, it is. There were quite a lot of crazy sound frames,
As a dance lover, I enjoy this dance immensely.
Indeed.
I remember how much fun I had the first time I was choreographed.
It's okay. With the right place for the lyrics and the sound framing,
It is a very detailed song that I would like to dance to once.
I want you to dance. I want you to cover.
Thank you for visiting.
It was crazy cool.
Beyooooonds not so much beautiful lines and such,
I don't have much of a pool or anything.
So I am really excited to see Tsubaki Factory's choreography.
I would love to cover this song for us someday.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!
The future is different. It's a little bit different.
And yet, when I walk next to you, I feel like we're in the same row.
Each path is a bumpy tale
Let me ask you something. The future is at your feet.
That's a signal that I can do it.
I don't want it. I don't want anything.
I'll get to that later. For now, move on.
Don't forget your shame
It has to be now.
The tailwind is rushing.
Youth is NO TIME
Always a little short.
You don't have time to hesitate.
It has to be you.
I certainly feel it.
You can't leave that behind.
everyone is better than just one person
Because I want to get real and close.
It has to be now.
You know, to be able to feel.
You're so talented!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
being with no place to go
Senses always go bye-bye.
Bye-bye beyond words
Are you ready?
Catch up! Come on, three, two, one.
Here. Jump in.
Even after the fact. Proof of my obsession.
Okay, that's fine. That's fine.
My tears, everyone's smile
Let's go grab him and take him with us right now.
It has to be now.
The tailwind is rushing.
Youth is NO TIME
Always a little short.
No, you don't cry on certain days.
so much as to cry
The day I longed for
Knowing that feeling
More than a promise
Strong and believable ties
Subtitle Kiyohiroi
It has to be now.
It has to be this one.
If you take my hand, it's a big no-no.
You can't lose, glory.
How long do you think it will take me to get to the place I longed to be?
You have to be alive.
I can definitely feel it.
One Chance that cannot be left behind
everyone is better than just one person
The Moon Filled with Serious Tricks
I want to see it with you now.
Words, music, arrangement by Miku Hatsune
Song: Hatsune Miku
The launch event at Live Chetta is now over~.
Yay!
So I'd like to hear what you think of what you did,
Then, Keiko Ishida, please.
It was the first time for me to perform a unit song at such a launch event,
It was a fresh feeling and a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Next, Mo-chan Kitahama.
Today was the first tea horse solo live performance in 2024,
The venue was very warm, and the crowd was really excited,
At the farewell party, I would wish everyone a Happy New Year,
It was a lot of fun to say hello and wish you a happy new year.
Yes.
And Tea Horse's first album Channel 1 has finally been released~!
Yay!
So I'm going to ask you to give me some recommendations,
Okay, then, Kami Ishida.
Yes, I do. The album begins with five new songs,
It is a 2-disc album with 23 songs in total,
As Miyuki mentioned earlier, three of the five new songs are unit songs,
The 10 tea horses are divided into three units, and they are performing in a way that is quite unique,
I hope everyone will pay attention to it.
Yes.
Okay, then, Ruri Hiromoto.
Yes, I have a new song called "Cha Cha Sing 2024 Tea Horse Ver.". And one of the 5 new songs is called "Cha Cha Sing 2024 Tea Horse Ver,
This song has more of a Japanese flavor than Berryz KOBO's previous songs,
The sound in the interludes is very different, for example,
The rest of the choreography was to be choreographed in a way that everyone could do it together,
I feel that we can do this together, incorporating the horse-like character of the tea ceremony,
We hope you all enjoy doing this together.
Yes, I am. So please listen to Channel 1 of "Tea Horse Ver." a lot.
Best regards.
These are the tea horses.
You're doing great, you're cool!
Shigion Akiyama of Tsubaki Factory, Beyooooonds, and Yutana Sato of Seasoning's present Halo! STE!
It is time to say goodbye. Here is an announcement.
Project 2024 Winter 3 of Us is now underway. Tsubaki Factory and Beyooooonds will be in Team A with Morning Musume。 Project 2024 Winter 3 of Us is now underway.
The next show will be in Osaka on January 20 and 21. If you are in the area, please check it out.
And Tsubaki Factory new album 3rd Moment will be released on February 21.
I feel that Tsubaki Factory's music has a really wide range, and I hope that you can feel the difference between our songs.
And Tsubaki Factory's major debut 7th anniversary live will be held on March 10 at Ichikawa City Cultural Hall.
We hope it will be a live performance that is a little unprecedented, so please come and visit us.
We, Tsubaki Factory, will participate in the 6th Nakagusuku Festival on February 27.
There will be many idols performing at the event at Shinjuku Rainy, and we, Tsubaki Factory, will do our best not to be outdone.
Beyooooonds will be released on Blu-ray in the spring of 2024 for the theater girls' club Biospy: The Missing Attache Case.
The Tokyo performance and the first Osaka performance are both included in the video, so please compare the two performances and enjoy.
And Hello! Project will be hosting the 2024 by Satomi Satoyama Movement for Carbon Neutrality at Makuhari Messe on March 30 and 31.
I look forward to this event very much every year.
We will do our best, so please come and visit us.
Hello! Ste is a channel where the members of Hello! Project appear more and more.
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to our channel.
Please.
The partners were Maho Akiyama of Tsubaki Factory, Beyooooonds, and Kana Satoyoshi of Seasonings.
Good-bye.
Thank you for watching.